export const MusicData = [
    {
        id:0,
        question:`Who recorded the song “I’m Black and I’m Proud”? `,
        options: [`Jamie Foxx`, ` Stevie Wonder`, `James Brown`, `Alicia Keys`],
        answer: `James Brown`
    },
    {
        id:1,
        question:`What decade is the hit single "On and on" by Gladys Knight & the Pips from?`,
        options: [`90s`, ` 50s`, `70s`, `60s`],
        answer: `70s`
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:`Which city is widely acknowledged as the birthplace of Hip Hop `,
        options: [`Brooklyn, NY`, ` Compton, LA`, `Brox, NY`, `Houston, TX`],
        answer: `Brox, NY`
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question:`In 1953, the song “Hound Dog” was released by this blues singer before Elvis Presley’s 1956 version. `,
        options: [`Bessie Smith`, ` Willie Mae “Big Mama” Thornton`, `Ethel Waters`, `Ruth Brown`],
        answer: `Willie Mae “Big Mama” Thornton`
    }, 
    {
        id:4,
        question:`This Renaissance man has a gift for producing, composing, arranging and performing! His work has influenced artists like Michael Jackson and Frank Sinatra and his keen ear and talents have made him the all-time most nominated Grammy artist in history.  `,
        options: [`Quincy Jones`, `Thelonious Monk`, `Lionel Richie`, `Stevie Wonder`],
        answer: `Quincy Jones`
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question:`This musician is hailed as the creator of “Afrobeat,” and used his music as a platform to call for political and social progression in and outside of `,
        options: [`Fela Kuti`, ` Bob Marley`, ` K’Naan`, `Gil Scott Heron `],
        answer: `Fela Kuti`
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question:`The legendary band Parliament Funkadelic helped usher in a revolutionary decade of Funk music... Their endless hits include songs like “Bring the Funk” and “Flash Light.” What kind of musical group did they begin as? Who recorded the song “I’m Black and I’m Proud”? `,
        options: [`Boys' Choir`, `Jazz Quartet`, `Barbershop Quartet`, `Doo Wop Group`],
        answer: `Doo Wop Group`
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:`Whose 1939 Easter Sunday concert at the Lincoln Memorial broke racial barriers and was seen as an important moment in the struggle for civil rights?  `,
        options: [`Marian Anderson`, `Shirley Horn`, `Pearl Bailey`, `Billie Holliday`],
        answer: `Marian Anderson`
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:`Which gospel singer would go on to be called the “Godmother of Rock-N-Roll?”`,
        options: [` Varetta Dillard`, ` Sister Rosetta Tharpe`, `Faye Adams`, ` Etta James`],
        answer: `Sister Rosetta Tharpe`
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:`What rappers real name is Clifford Harris? `,
        options: [`Ludacris`, `Chingy`, `T.I.`, ` 2 Chainz`],
        answer: `T.I.`
    },
    
]
